我不会忘记Gibbs抓住这变态的那天
I will never forget the day that Gibbs caught this psycho.
你那时候就认识他了?
You knew Gibbs back then?
不. 我那时是在乔治城的一名大三学生 有两年的时间
No. I was a junior at Georgetown. And for two years,
城里每个女的都害怕在晚上出门
every woman in D.C. was afraid to go out at night.
那肯定是很难了
Must have been tough.
是啊, 你是不知道 我的确是欠了Gibbs的
Yeah,you have no idea. I actually owe Gibbs
让我在进大学后睡了一个整晚的好觉
for the first full night of sleep I got in college.
Mm, 我是指约会
Mm,I meant dating.
对, 没错, 约会很难
Yes,yes,dating was tough.
现在那方面需要什么帮助吗, Paula?
Need any help with that now,Paula?
不, Tony, 谢谢
No,Tony,thank you.
我经历过也做过了
I've been there and I've done that.
哎呀!
Ouch.
你和女人的问题就在于你关注在哪儿
Your problem with women is where you're focused.
哪儿?
Where?
这里
Here.
是个镜子
It's a mirror.
快速问答
Quick question.
粉红色的. 它们吃起来是不是草莓味的?
The pink ones.Do they taste like strawberry starburst?
我以为你说过你没有和什么人约会
I thought you said you weren't seeing anyone.
我没说
I'm not.
是用于一些情形中的
It's for my complexion.
情形, 有名字吧?
Complexion got a name?
Tony, 你别来这一套
Tony,you so don't want to go there.
只是告诉我那个人别是个探员 因为我真的不认为我能...
Just tell me it's not another agent, 'cause I really don't think I can...
他叫Bob, 他是个律师
His name's Bob,and he's a lawyer.
太巧了. 我讨厌律师
What a coincidence.I hate lawyers.
我知道. 我也是
I know. So do I.
那就是为什么只是个性关系罢了
That's why it's purely a sexual relationship.
那个跟我有什么关系?
Well,what would that make me?
错大了. 如果你不...
A big mistake.If you do not...
...把避孕丸还给我 我会把你胳膊给拧折了
...give me my birth control pills, I'm going to break your arm.
拿了杯咖啡
Got that coffee.
你在那儿呆了很久了?
Have you been there long?
呃, 时间长得可以说 "不, 长官, Cassidy探员"
Uh,long enough to say, "No,ma'am,Agent Cassidy."
好吧, 答得好
Okay,good answer.
谢谢
Thank you.
我让她那么做的
I let her do that.
谢谢
Thank you.
那是谁?
Who's that?
Kyle Boone
Kyle Boone.
实习的, 他是个恶名昭彰的连环杀手
He's an infamous serial killer,
在90年代在城里制造了恐怖 知道了吧
Probie terrorized the District in the 90s. Come on.
22名女性失踪了, 找到了5具尸体
22 women went missing and five bodies were found.
那家伙只犯了一个错误
Guy only made one mistake.
他杀了个漂亮的女长官
He killed a petty officer.
Gibbs抓住他的?
Gibbs caught him?
定于周六进行政府批准的死刑裁决
Scheduled for a government-sanctioned dirt-nap on Saturday.
在合上电闸前他想和Gibbs谈谈
He wants to talk to Gibbs before they flip the switch.
为什么?
Why?
声称他会告诉他们那些尸体在哪里
Claims he's gonna tell them where the bodies are.
做什么把那东西放在我的屏幕上?
What the hell is that doing on my screen?
- 呃, 我没放在那儿, 老大 - 谁做的, McGee?
- Uh,I didn't put it there,boss. - Who did,McGee?
实习的, 让我来处理
Probie,let me handle this.
老大...
Boss...
她干的
she did it.
我们听说你在见...
We heard you were interviewing...
Kyle Boone, 我们猜我们可能 能够提供些支持
Kyle Boone,and we assumed that we would be providing backup.
你们的听说有误, Cassidy 我没有见什么人
You heard wrong,Cassidy. I'm not interviewing anyone.
哦, 那好, 你可能会想让 弗吉尼亚州长知道的
Oh,well,then you might want to let the Governor of Virginia
因为MTAC(多重威胁预警中心)已让他 待命, 在等着你的电话呢
know,since MTAC has him standing by,waiting for your call.
给她弄张桌子
Find her a desk.
- 那一张... - 不行, 给占了
- Is that one... - No,it's taken.
有一整个星期和Gibbs打照面 我都能嗅出有趣的味道了
A whole week of T.A.D. with Gibbs. I can smell the fun already.
那一个月可不好过
Well,it's been a tough month.
现在他差不多恨所有人, Paula
Right now he pretty much hates everyone,Paula.
包括他自己
Including himself.
你们的司长告诉我你今天下午
I was told by your Director that you would personally
想要单独见Kyle Boone, Gibbs探员
be interviewing Kyle Boone this afternoon,Agent Gibbs.
Shepard司长告诉了您错误的消息 州长
Director Shepard was misinformed,Governor.
和Kyle Boone谈就是浪费时间
Talking to Kyle Boone would be a waste of time.
也许是的, 但如果确有可能他对你
Possibly,but if there's even a chance that he would reveal
说出来那些受害人的位置, 我们得试试
to you the location of his victims,we have to take it.
我不同意, 长官
I disagree,sir.
他已经有十年的时间来好好想想了 为什么他现在回心转意了?
He's had ten years to think about it. Why the change of heart now?
就我的经验来说
In my experience,
临近死亡的人倾向于重新评价他们 的生命历程
men facing imminent death tend to reevaluate the course of their lives.
- 很多人会寻求原谅 - 相信我, 长官
- Most seek forgiveness. - You trust me,sir.
Boone有很多种兴趣
Boone had a lot of interests.
原谅可不是其中之一
Forgiveness wasn't one of them.
你怎么能这么肯定?
How can you be so sure?
我花了五个月来审问他
I spent five months interrogating him.
十年前
A decade ago.
- 人会变的 - 人, 长官
- People change. - People,sir.
可能会
Maybe.
Kyle Boone不会
Not Kyle Boone.
你是在拒绝和他会面?
Are you refusing to meet with him?
我是在拒绝娱乐一个谋杀狂
I'm refusing to entertain a homicidal maniac
他折磨并杀害了22名女性, 长官
who tortured and killed 22 women,sir.
我以前玩过了那种游戏
I have played that game before.
对于那些失去了女儿, 姐妹或母亲的
And the hundreds of family members who lost a daughter
几百名家庭成员?
a sister or a mother?
我该怎么和他们说?
What do I tell them?
不管在接下来的几天里Kyle Boone 会说什么
That no matter Kyle Boone says in the next few days,
到了周六时, 长官, 您得确保 他给烤了
come Saturday,sir,you're going to make sure he fries.
你将他受法, 我们都欠你个感激债
We all owe you a debt of gratitude for bringing him
Gibbs探员, 但是, 呃... 你让我没得选择
to justice,Agent Gibbs,but,uh... you leave me little choice.
对不起
I am sorry.
-= 海军罪案调查处 NCIS=- 第三季 第三集
SYNC:YTET-wk120 -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
长官! 有个从MTAC来的找你的
Sir! We've got a high
优先传输连接
priority transmission coming through for you in MTAC.
- 谁的? - 海军部长
- From who? - Secretary of the Navy.
哦, 往好的方面想想吧
Well,look on the bright side.
好的方面是什么?
What is the bright side?
你只会在这儿一个礼拜
You're only here a week.
为什么不能用Kate的桌子?
Why couldn't I sit at Kate's desk?
很大程度上是因为那仍是Kate的桌子
Mostly,because it's still Kate's desk.
她是个出色的探员
She was a great agent.
是的
Yep.
你是怎么处理的?
How are you handling it?
和处理所有的事情一样-- 试着不去想它
Same way I handle everything-- try not to think about it.
不起作用的时候呢?
And when that doesn't work?
总是会有垃圾食品的
There's always junk food.
听上去不怎么健康, Tony
Doesn't sound very healthy,Tony.
要不那样, 要不就在我的地下室里 开始建艘船
It's either that or I start building a boat in my basement.
你从你的公寓搬走了?
Did you move from your apartment?
没有. 现在你知道我的两难了
No. Now you see my dilemma.
如果你想谈谈的话, 我会在的
If you ever do want to talk about it,I'm here for you.
好吗?
Okay?
你说真的?
You mean that?
是的, 当然我是说真的
Yes,of course I mean that.
好的
Okay.
好吧, 那么, 我来问问你
Well,then,let me ask you something.
Bobbie在床上表现如何?
What's Bobbie like in bed?
Kate是对的. 你是真的, 真的可怜 DiNozzo
Kate was right.You are truly, truly pathetic,DiNozzo.
呃, 你们俩可能会想要开始工作 Gibbs朝这边来了, 而且看上去不高兴
Uh,you two might want to get busy. Gibbs's headed this way and he looks pissed.
他会不会听了州长的?
Think he caved to the Governor?
- 不可能 - 不可能
- No way. - No way.
如果Gibbs不想做什么, 他就不会的
If Gibbs doesn't want to do something,he doesn't.
不管是谁要求
No matter who's asking.
你要去哪儿, 老大?
Where you going,boss?
萨塞克斯州监狱
Sussex State Prison,
去见Kyle Boone
interviewing Kyle Boone.
后面都会在那儿耗着
Be gone the rest of the day.
没错, 你俩肯定是把他给看死了
Yep,you two sure have him pegged.
周一我们把他移到死囚牢房了
We moved Boone to death watch on Monday.
就是那时候他决定他想要谈谈
That's when he decided he wanted to talk.
在弗吉尼亚这儿我们的做法有些不一样
We do things a little different here in Virginia.
被判死刑的可以选择:
The condemned get a choice:
注射致命药物或是电刑
lethal injection or death by electrocution.
Boone是选择电椅的第一个人
Boone is the first one to choose the chair.
- 应受到更严厉的 - Gibbs探员?
- Deserves worse. - Special Agent Gibbs?
我是Adam O'Neill Kyle Boone的律师
真是很感谢你能来
I'm Adam O'Neill,Kyle Boone's attorney. I really appreciate your coming.
我, 呃... 我理解你不愿意来这儿
I,uh... I understand your reluctance here.
但我确实相信我委托人的意图是 发自真心的
But I truly believe that my client's intentions are sincere.
我逮捕你委托人的那天
The day I arrested your client,
我们在他的冰箱里发现了两根 人类女性的舌头
we found two human female tongues in his refrigerator.
我对案子很熟, Gibbs探员
I'm familiar with the case,Agent Gibbs.
真的? 你对他的受害人的名字熟吗?
Really? You familiar with the names of his victims?
你看, 我不是来这儿谈过去的
Look,I'm not here to talk about the past.
我来这儿是想要救一个人的命
I'm here trying to save a man's life.
Boone想要做个交易?
Boone wants a deal?
不是. Boone先生想为他的罪行坐上电椅
No. Mr. Boone wants the chair for his crimes.
我是想要让他得到终生监禁
I'm the one hoping to get him life in prison.
祝你好运了
Good luck with that.
Gibbs探员, 拜托
Agent Gibbs,please.
在这儿我只在做我的工作
I'm just trying to do my job here.
可能一起的话, 我们能帮那些受害人 的家庭找到些终结
Maybe together,we can both help the victims' families find some closure.
周六一定到吧
Be there Saturday.
你会看见他们得到的
You'll be able to see them get that.
这边走, 先生们
Right this way,gentlemen.
事实上, 没有听从我的建议
Well,actually,against my advice,
Boone先生选择了单独见Gibbs探员
Mr. Boone has elected to meet with Agent Gibbs alone.
如果需要的话, 会有个守卫候在外面
There'll be a guard out here if you need him.
不需要
I won't.
很高兴再次见到你, Jethro
Nice to see you again,Jethro.
我还不确定你是不是会来 但是... 你来了.
I wasn't sure if you'd come, but... here you are.
给你两分钟的时间. 说吧
You've got two minutes.Start talking.
要知道, 你看上去差不多还是一样..
You know,you look almost the same...
除了头发
except the hair.
什么时候开始变灰白的?
When did it go gray?
那些尸体在哪儿?
Where are the bodies?
会说到的
We'll get to that.
有些事情我想要先问问你
There's just a few things I need to ask you first.
我猜他们给你看了我的纪念品了?
I guess they showed you my souvenirs?
那个罐子里有不到20个人的
There weren't 20 in that jar.
你是说..?
Your point?
我常想你是在虚报数目
I always thought you were padding your account.
哦. 给我下套? 毁我声誉?
Oh. Baiting me? Denigrating my rep?
得了. 你知道那方法不会对我起 作用的, Jethro
Come on. You know that approach never worked on me,Jethro.
1分38秒
A minute 38.
我们就不能聊聊吗? 聚一聚?
Can't we just chat for a bit? Catch up?
你太太怎么样了?
How's the wife?
她离开你了, 对吗?
She left you,didn't she?
我试过警告你的
I tried to warn you about that.
女人不会懂得像我们这样的男人
Women can't understand men like us.
你明白吗, Boone?
You got what,Boone?
还有三天活头?
Three days left?
感觉如何?
How's it feel?
有些害怕
I'm kind of terrified.
考虑到我以前的所做所为, 这很奇怪
Weird,considering my former activities.
据说在电椅上死掉得花上四分种
They say it can take up to four minutes to die in the chair.
就我个人来说?
Me,personally?
我希望能久得多
I'm hoping it takes a lot longer.
你真是变了
You really have changed.
以前的Gibbs从不会这么粗率
The old Gibbs would never be this abrupt.
你再婚了吗?
Did you remarry?
- 你只剩不到一分钟 - 好吧, 好吧, 太针对个人了
- You got less than a minute. - Okay,okay,too personal.
那么, 关于, 呃, NCIS的 Caitlin Todd探员呢?
Now,what about,uh,NCIS Special Agent Caitlin Todd?
我们能谈谈她吗?
Can we talk about her?
我在报上看见她照片了
I saw her picture in thePost.
听说是给恐怖分子给射杀的?
They said she was shot by a terrorist?
你有没有像我告诉的那样减少咖啡因 的摄入?
Did you cut back on the caffeine like I told you?
周六见
See you Saturday.
来吧, Gibbs. 我只和你说笑来的!
Come on,Gibbs.I was just having some fun with you!
你不能离开
You can't leave.
你来这儿是因为你得听从命令 就像是个优秀的海军陆战队员
You're here because you're following orders,like a good Marine.
对吧, Gunny?
Right,Gunny?
我会告诉你她们在哪儿的
I'll tell you where they are.
所有的她们在的地方
Where they all are.
可是要比22个来的多, Jethro
There's more than 22,Jethro.
多得多
Lots more.
- 他在哪儿, Timothy? - 呃, 谁?
- Where is he,Timothy? - Uh,who?
Gibbs, 可恶!
Gibbs,damn it.
你知不知道好的和坏的胆固醇水平 之间的差别, Tonny?
Do you even know the difference between good and bad cholesterol,Tony?
不, 但我猜那是和口味有关
No,but I'm assuming it has something to do with taste.
你最近的血液测试结果就是坏的
Bad is what came back on your last blood test.
扔了这个
Dispose of this.
嘿, 嘿, 那可是花了我16块, 那披萨
Hey,hey,that cost me 16 bucks,that pizza.
你到了我这年纪就会感谢我了
You'll thank me when you're my age.
- 可你总是吃披萨 - 没错
- But you eat pizza all the time. - Exactly.
我真是看不出来有什么关联
I don't really see the connection here.
哦, 当然你看不出来, 你又不是医生
Well,of course you wouldn't, you're not a doctor.
Gibbs在哪儿?
Where is Gibbs?
萨克塞斯州监狱, 在见Kyle Boone
Sussex State Prison, interviewing Kyle Boone.
- 他说他不会去的 - 他是没有
- He said he wasn't going. - He wasn't.
直到海军部长命令他去
Until the SecNav ordered him to.
- 谁同他一起? - 没人
- Who's with him? - No one.
你知不知道十年前那个精神病对 Gibbs的影响?
Have you any idea the effect that psychopath had on Gibbs ten years ago?
考虑到Gibbs对他的私生活公开到 什么程度...
Considering how open Gibbs is about his personal life...
呃, 不, 一点不知道
uh,no,not a clue.
他不应该一个人去的
He should not have gone alone.
Ducky, 这是... 这是Gibbs 我肯定他会没事的
Ducky,it's... it's Gibbs. I'm sure he'll be fine.
你说说倒容易
That's easy for you to say.
那一次你是不必经受这个
You didn't have to live through this the last time.
DiNozzo
DiNozzo.
哪里?
Where?
是的, 明白, 老大. 我们就来
Yeah,I got it,boss. We're on our way.
Cassidy, 准备出发 Gibbs想让你去现场
Cassidy,saddle up. Gibbs wants you in the field.
- Boone家族农场 - 想让我?
- Boone family farm. - Wants me?
正是他说的. 出发
That's what he said.Let's roll.
十年前和现在的区别, Ducky?
The difference between ten years ago and today,Ducky?
我们的Gibbs回来了
We have Gibbs' back.
还有另外个区别, Tony
There's another difference,Tony.
十年前, Gibbs是个很不一样的人
Ten years ago, Gibbs was a very different man.
你意思是他实际上更小器?
You mean he was actually meaner?
不是, 恰恰相反
No,quite the opposite.
他是...
He was...
他挺像你的
he was a lot like you.
这儿有什么?
What do we got?
我能给你节约些时间, Gibbs 我的尺寸是34...
I can save you the time,Gibbs. My measurements are 34...
26-34
26-34.
120磅. 我是对的, 不是吗?
120 pounds. I'm right,aren't I?
你是不是在我睡着的时候称量了我?
Did you weigh and measure me in my sleep?
我是罪案现场的素描专家
I'm a crime-scene sketch expert.
- 是我的工作 - 你会做的
- It's what I do. - You'll do.
Gibbs, 再一次, 你是用这样的办法 让个女的感觉这么特殊
Gibbs,again,you have such a way of making a gal feel so special.
戴上这个
Put this on.
McGee?
- 在, 老大? - 你可能会想要套上护膝
Yeah,boss?You might want to wear kneepads.
我们会有护膝吗?
Do we even have kneepads?
设备清单是Kate的事
Equipment inventory's Kate's job.
你可能会想要问问...
You might want to ask...
你知道我们到底是在做什么吗?
Do you know what the hell we're doing?
跟着Gibbs走
Following Gibbs' lead.
- 什么事情? - 我不知道
- On what? - I don't know.
你不知道, 这压根不会让你操心吗?
You don't know and that doesn't bother you at all?
你会习惯的
You get used to it.
是啊, 那正是我担心的
Yeah,that's what I'm afraid of.
这个地方肯定已经被翻过十来次了 老大
This place must have been gone over a dozen times,boss.
这儿不可能会有什么尸体的
No way there's any bodies in here.
不是在找尸体, Tony
Not looking for bodies,Tony.
Boone在这儿由他叔叔养大
Boone was raised here by his uncle.
他母亲是个妓女 在他12岁时离开了
His mother was a prostitute, she left town when he was 12.
- 那我们在找什么? - 证据
- Then what are we looking for? - Proof.
Boone发誓就在这儿
Boone swears it's here,
我们没有找过的唯一的地方就是 烟囱里面了
and the only place we didn't look is inside this chimney.
我想我发现了什么
I think I got something.
不是. 那只是又一只死鸟
No.That's just another dead bird.
哦, 真恶心
Oh,it's disgusting.
我打赌你在NCIS签到的时候这没有 在手册里, 实习的
Bet this wasn't in the brochure when you signed up for NCIS,Probie.
要知道, 你早先说错了
You know,you were wrong earlier.
什么?
About what?
她要比120磅重
She weighs more than a buck 20.
- 对不起 - 她是故意的
- Sorry. - She did that on purpose.
好了. 哦, 哦, 我拿到... 就在烟道边上
Okay.Oh,no,I got... it's right here by the flue.
我拿到了. 好了, 我下来了
I got it.Okay,I'm coming down.
终于. 要知道, 你应该脱下你的...
Finally.You know,you could have taken your...
- 天哪 - 我不对
- Jeez. - My bad.
看来像是本书
Looks like a book.
哦, 肯定能有30页
Oh,there must be 30 pages there.
不止
More.
是用什么刻进了她们的背?
What's carved into their backs?
是他的电话卡, McGee
It's his calling card,McGee.
有什么不对吗?
Something wrong?
关于我母亲的这部分, John 好了些, 但它还得要加工
This sectionon my mother,John, is better,but it still needs work.
我在试着让她更有人情味, Kyle
I was trying to humanize her,Kyle.
别
Don't.
你找到了对吧, Jethro?
You find it all right,Jethro?
我想如果你没找到的话是不会来的
I guess you wouldn't be here if you didn't.
我相信你还没见过我的传记作家 John Briggs
I don't believe you've met my biographer, John Briggs.
Gibbs探员, 很高兴.
Special Agent Gibbs, it is a pleasure.
这几个月来我一直在试着安排个时间 来见见你
I've been trying to schedule an interview with you for months.
你不得不将离开了, Briggs
You're going to have to leave now,Briggs.
我已由弗吉尼亚州批准特别许可了 守卫
I've been granted special permission by the state of Virginia to be here,Warden.
不再有了
Not anymore.
你下次要见Boone
Next time you see Boone,
他就会让你出些意外的
he'll have a thunderbolt shooting out of his ass.
嘿, 我是...
Hey,I was...
我给保证过在以后的三天我可以自由 进出
I was guaranteed full access for the next three days.
守卫要求你离开
The warden asked you to leave.
别让他再次要求
Don't make him ask you again.
你得谅解Gibbs探员, John
You'll have to excuse Agent Gibbs,John.
他终于得以窥见我告诉过他的世界了
He's finally gotten a glimpse into the world I've been telling him about.
剪贴簿?
Scrapbook?
你找到了他的剪贴簿? 什么时候...会发表出来?
You found his scrapbook? When... when will it be released?
小子, 如果你想自己走着出去的话
Son,if you want to walk out of here under your own power,
我建议你现在就离开
I suggest you leave now.
John真是个了不起的作家
John really is a wonderful writer.
你知道, 他花费了多年试图来了解我
You know,he's spent years trying to understand me.
不幸的是, 看来他只是从未合格过
Unfortunately,he just never seemed to measure up.
对谁?
To who?
你那妓女母亲?
Your prostitute mom?
或是你的父亲?
Or your father?
某个在兜里有几块钱的乡巴佬John
Some hick john with a few extra bucks in his pocket.
事实上, 我提到了你, Jethro
Actually,I was referring to you, Jethro.
演出结束
Show's over.
埋尸处在哪儿?
Where's the dumping ground?
你最后再给我看看我的剪贴簿
You show me my scrapbook one last time
我就会给你画张即便是个海军陆战 队员都能依照的图
and I'll draw you a map even a Marine can follow.
不行. 她们已经够遭罪了
No. They've suffered enough.
那么, 我们就成僵局了
Well,we're at an impasse.
你还要继续和我玩这个游戏吗, Boone?
You're going to keep playing this game with me,Boone?
我从来没把这个看成是个游戏, Jethro
I've never considered any of this a game,Jethro.
你知道的
You know that.
- 不管怎样. 我改规则了 - 怎么改法?
- Whatever.I'm changing the rules. - How so?
我已经见识了你的世界
I've seen your world.
现在你将在我的世界中耗尽你那悲惨 的一生中仅剩的部分了
Now you're going to spend what's left of your miserable life in mine.
好吧, 听着, 我的现场探查实习的 小朋友们
All right,listen up,my little probationary field agents.
你们将会目睹一次将个最高安全级的
You're about to witness the transfer
囚犯转到我们这粗陋设施的过程
of a maximum security prisoner to our humble facility.
他到达时, 他就是我们唯一的责任
While he's here, he's our sole responsibility.
- 哦, 很抱歉. 我烦着你了吗? - 天哪, 他就没停过吗?
- Oh,I'm sorry.Am I boring you? - My God,does he ever stop?
我只是很高兴那不是我
I'm just glad it's not me.
现在10点. 没理由现在就把Boone 带到这里
It's 10:00.Doesn't make any sense bringing Boone here now.
Gibbs想把他置于一个不熟悉的环境 让他失衡
Gibbs is trying to put him on unfamiliar ground,throw him off balance.
因为在十年前这招很管用?
Because that worked so well ten years ago?
- 现在有什么不一样? - 我有, Cassidy
- What's different now? - I am,Cassidy.
挺胸. 精神些, 实习的们
Stand tall.Lace up,Probies.
我知道我能指望上你的, Jethro
I knew I could count on you,Jethro.
再回到家真好
It's good to be home again.
是的. 回家真好
Yeah.Good to be home.
这家伙整晚都在扮雕像
Guy's been impersonating a statue all night.
据守卫说, 他一动也没动
According to the watch, he hasn't moved a muscle.
真让人毛骨悚然
It's creepy.
Gibbs什么时候会开始他的审问?
When is Gibbs going to start his interrogation?
在他准备好的时候
When he's ready.
你可能想要告诉他要他快点
Well,you might want to tell him to hurry.
在安排的Boone死刑执行前他只剩 不到48小时了
He's got less than 48 hours before Boone's scheduled to be executed.
我有个更好的主意, Paula
I've got a better idea,Paula.
为什么你不去告诉他呢?
Why don't you tell him?
因为我不蠢
'Cause I'm not stupid.
不会
No.
在你的所有特质当中
Of all the things you are,
愚蠢决不在其中
stupid definitely isn't one of them.
谢谢
Thank you.
好吧, 那究竟是什么意思?
Okay,what's that supposed to mean?
没什么. 顺便, Bobert怎么样了?
Nothing.By the way,how's Bobert?
怎么, 你嫉妒吗?
Why,are you jealous?
就那个律师? 算了吧
Of a lawyer?Give me a break.
- 他很有钱 - 钱不代表一切
- He's very rich. - Money isn't everything.
他有华盛顿红皮队的季赛票--
He's got season tickets to the Redskins--
私人的顶部包厢
private sky box.
真为他高兴
I'm happy for him.
我差点忘了... 他开的是辆法拉利
And I almost forgot... he drives a Ferrari.
- 红色的 - 像雷诺Magnum
- Red. - Like Magnum.
哦, 不错啊
Well,that's nice.
不是吗?
Isn't it?
你知道什么会更棒?
You know what's even nicer?
我现在看到的. 维多利亚的秘密 Cassidy探员
My current view.Victoria's Secret. Agent Cassidy.
哦, 随你享受多久, DiNozzo探员
Well,you enjoy it as long as you can,Agent DiNozzo.
因为那是你能得到的最近的距离
Because that's as close as you're going to get.
Cassidy?
查查Boone的安全细节
Check Boone's security detail.
明白
You got it.
- 我来帮帮她 - 等等
- I'll give her a hand with that. - Wait.
- 那是为什么? - 让她影响到你
- What was that for? - Letting her get to you.
老大, 我不是在让她...
Boss,I was not letting her get...
别让这事再发生了
Won't let it happen again.
谢谢
Thanks.
是给Abby的
It's for Abby.
去看看她从Boone的剪贴簿本确认了 多少名受害人
Go find out how many victims she ID'd from Boone's scrapbook.
在剪贴簿里有27位女性, McGee
(缺一句)
就我所知道的, 她们是按被杀的先后 次序来排列的
And as far as I can tell,they're in the order that they were killed.
现在, Boone已承认杀死了22个人
Now,Boone has admitted to killing 22,
这和FBI发出的照片和档案相符
which matches with the photos and the files that the FBI sent over.
会让你认为我们还有五名Jane Doe (不知名的女性受害人)
Which would make you think that we'd be left with five Jane Does,
可你错了
but you'd be wrong
因为我知道
'cause I know
第一个受害人是谁
who the first victim is.
我说的你是一个字也没听进去
You're not listening to a word I'm saying.
我怀孕了, McGee
I'm pregnant,McGee.
双胞胎
Twins.
还没有告诉老爸
Haven't told the father yet.
是Gibbs的
It's Gibbs.
我知道这不对
I know it's wrong,
可是他那银发真是挺能撩拨人的
but something about his silver hair just gets me all tingly inside.
打断一小会儿, 我想我要吐了
Excuse me for a sec. I think I'm going to vomit.
我在开玩笑, Tony
I'm joking,Tony.
除了关于Gibbs银发的那部分 那真是性感
Except for the part about Gibbs'hair.That is really hot.
- McGee又不搭理我了 - 很容易修好
- McGee's ignoring me again. - Easily fixable.
干嘛? 我做了什么?
What? What'd I do?
别不理Abby. 她很敏感
Stop ignoring Abby.She's sensitive.
对不起. 我正全神贯注 我想我知道就算Gibbs不和他谈
I'm sorry.I was concentrating. I think that I know how we can
我们怎么可以找到Boone的受害人了
find Boone's victims without Gibbs having to talk to him.
在这些图片中的一些里面
There are distinctive geographical and man-made features
有些特别的地理特性和人造的特色
in several of these pictures.
有条河流... 这可能是座桥...
There's a stream... and what may be a bridge...
上面这儿, 看上去像是电力线
Up here,there appears to be a power line.
或是照片上的一些脏东西
Or some dirt on a picture.
如果我能做一个地面图
If I can make a land plot,
通过计算这些点之间的距离来做出 个数值范围
create scale by computing the distances between these points,
- 那我们就能... - 好了
- then we can... - Okay.
河流和电力线?
Streams and power lines?
光搜个小郡就得花上好几年
It would take years searching
McGee, 更别提是个州了
just one county,McGee, never mind a state.
对我们来说, 没错, Tony 可对计算机来说不是的
Yeah,for us,Tony, but not for a computer.
- 卫星成像? - 正是
- Satellite imagery? - Exactly.
我应该想到那个的
I should have thought of that.
我只是需要想个办法来算出 准确的范围
I just need to figure out a way to calculate an accurate scale.
偏光照相机有固定的焦距
Polaroid cameras have a fixed focal length.
会是个好开端
It's a good start.
呃, 我得需要个已知的尺寸
Uh,I'm going to need one known measurement.
选个人, 我把她的数据调出来
Pick one body and I'll pull her stats.
有三个已知的向量就行了
Three known vectors should do it.
- 四个可能会... - 好了, 好了
- Four would be... - Okay,okay.
这种古怪的谈话也够了
Enough with the geek-speak.
Gibbs想知道我们确认了多少受害人
Gibbs wants to know how many victims we ID'd.
所有的, 除了在剪贴簿里的最后四个
All,except for the last four in the scrapbook.
我们正在将她们与Gibbs把Boone
We're running them against missing persons reports
投进监狱前的失踪人员报告进行比对 还没有对上的
prior to Gibbs putting Boone behind bars.No matches yet.
最为显眼的那个人就是第一个受害者
The one that stands out the most is the first victim.
她是在1974失踪的
She disappeared in 1974.
你确定吗, Abs?
Are you sure about that,Abs?
那时Boone还只是个孩子
Boone was just a kid back then.
我知道
I know.
而且也表明他的妈妈没有遗弃他
And it turns out his mother did not abandon him.
她是他的第一个受害者
She was his first kill.
你不必再这么做了, 你知道
You don't have to do this again, you know.
你错了, Duck, 我必须
You're wrong,Duck,I do.
他不会告诉你那些可怜姑娘在哪里的
He's never going to tell you where those poor girls are.
我知道
I know that.
那为什么?
Then why?
因为十年前, 我突破不了他
Because ten years ago, I couldn't break him.
不, 可你做到了其他人做不到的
No,but you did what no one else could;
你逮住了这狗娘养的
you caught the son of a bitch.
我应该杀了他
I should have killed him.
两天后, 就可以调过来了
And in two days, that will be rectified.
作为个朋友让我来告诉你
I'm telling you as a friend,
是时候放开这个了
it's time to let this one go.
还不行, Ducky
Not yet,Ducky.
因为这个案子你已经失去了个关系
You already lost one relationship as a resultof this case.
我意思是, 她是个很好的女孩
I mean,she was a wonderful girl,
- 而你忽略了... - 她离开了我, Duck!
- and you neglected... - She left me,Duck!
我没有离开她!
I didn't leave her!
不, 你使她不可能再留着了
No,you made it impossible for her to stay.
好了, 把他带上来. 确保有人押送
Okay,send him up. Make sure he's escorted.
我会让Gibbs知道的
I'll let Gibbs know.
舒服吗?
Comfortable?
- 是的. 事实上, 我... - 这是个修辞方面的问题, 女士
- Yeah.Matter of fact,I... - It was a rhetorical question,lady.
Wow. 我还没意识到你对你的桌子 有多么敏感
Wow. I never realized how sensitive you were about your desk.
关于我还有很多东西你没意识到 Cassidy
There's a lot about me you don't realize,Cassidy.
- Gibbs在哪儿? - 审讯中
- Where's Gibbs? - Interrogation.
Boone的律师在这里
Well,Boone's lawyer is here.
他声称对于他的委托人被转移这事 他没有被通知
He claims he wasn't notified about his client's being moved
他想要和你谈谈
and he wants to talk to him.
哦, Gibbs不喜欢等人. 你最好是
Ooh,Gibbs doesn't like to be kept waiting.You better go
进去那儿并自己告诉他. 我去拿衣服
right in there and tell him yourself. I'll get the suit.
终于
Finally.
那么这次我们从哪儿开始呢, Jethro?
So where should we start this time, Jethro?
我的童年?
My childhood?
我把带到这儿来不是要谈的, Boone
I didn't bring you in here to talk,Boone.
那么, 你决定让我再看看我的剪贴簿?
So,you decided to let me see my photographs again?
我告诉过你, 那是不会发生的
I told you,that's not going to happen.
有趣
Interesting.
我能问问为什么我会在这儿吗?
May I ask why I'm here then?
州府希望我能得到你那些 受害人的位置
The State is hoping that I'll get the location of your victims.
我相信那需要某种形式的沟通
I believe that requires some form of communication.
我说的是"州府", 我?
I said,"the state." Me?
根本不会去试
Not even going to try.
但你经常试的, Jethro 这就是为什么我喜欢你
But you always try,Jethro. That's why I like you.
我已经把你弄出那体系了, Boone
I've taken you out of the system, Boone.
你会孤单地坐在这里
You're going to sit here alone,
在上电椅烤前没有任何的与人接触
without any human contact until you fry.
游戏现在结束了
The game ends now.
这个房间带回了那么多记忆
This room brings back so many memories.
不是吗?
Doesn't it?
Gibbs探员? 说句话, 谢谢
Special Agent Gibbs? A word,please.
听上去那个死了的女人有个替代的了
Sounds like you replaced your dead female.
有机会让我能见见这个吗?
Any chance I can meet this one?
那么, 如果你需要我, 我就在这儿
Well,I'll be here if you need me.
什么?!
What?!
Boone的律师在这里
Boone's attorney's here.
地方法院检查官担心如果我们拒绝他去 见他的委托人
The D.A.'s afraid if we deny him access to his client,
那么他会去找个同情的法官并有借口
then he'll find a sympathetic judge and have cause to have
- 让死刑执行延后 - 明白了
- the execution delayed. - I got it.
嘿, 我需要和我的委托人进行特许 的会谈
Look,I need a privileged conversation with my client.
意思是, Gibbs探员
Meaning,Agent Gibbs,
我要你们将观察室清干净, 所有的 麦克风也要给关了
I want your observation room cleared and all microphones turned off.
- 就那样吗, 法律顾问? - 目前是的, 探员
- That's it,counselor? - For now,Agent.
Tony?
好了, 等一等
Yeah,hold on a second.
先搜搜他...
Search him first...
彻底地
thoroughly.
真让我激赏
I'm impressed.
它真起作用的
It's actually working.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在我们要做的就是扫描卫星成像
Now all we have to do is scan through 800,000 miles
的80万英里, 祈祷我们能走运
of satellite imagery and pray we get lucky.
我是个科学家, McGee
I am a scientist,McGee.
运气和这个和/或我们没什么关系
Luck has nothing to do with it and/or us.
好吧, 那你怎么解释像是Gibbs的直觉 那样的东西呢?
Okay,then how do you explain something like Gibbs's gut?
哦, 那容易
Well,that's easy.
Gibbs走运
Gibbs is lucky.
- 可你刚才说是... - 他不是科学家
- But you just said that... - He's not a scientist.
Gibbs探员
Agent Gibbs,
如果我的委托人在这里的期间 发生了什么事
if anything happens to my client while he's here,
我想让你知道我会让你
I want you to know I am going to hold you
个人负责...
personally responsible...
你有我的保证, 他会有良好的健康 等着他的死刑
You have my word he will be in perfect health for his execution.
护送O'Neill先生离开这幢楼 Cassidy探员
Escort Mr. O'Neill out of my building, Special Agent Cassidy.
你会从我这儿得到消息的
You'll be hearing from me.
走吧
Let's go.
你还要回那儿去吗, 老大?
You going back in there,Boss?
- 是的, 也许 - Gibbs
- Yeah,maybe. - Gibbs.
Gibbs, 是Abby. McGee和我认为 我们可能已经找到了
Gibbs,it's Abby. McGee and I think we might have found
Boone的弃尸地. 我们是在我实验室 里的屏幕上找到的
Boone's dumping ground. We've got it on the screen in my lab.
他们认为他们可能已经找到了 他的弃尸场所
They think they may have found his dumping ground.
我在看的是什么东西?
What am I looking at?
开动啊, Mc-Key
Take it,Mc-Key.
我意思是, um, 那McGee探员
I mean,um,very Special Agent McGee.
那些受害人被折磨, 杀害并可能被 埋的可能地点
Probable site where the victims were tortured,killed and perhaps buried.
- 想知道我们是怎么做的吗? - 不想
- You want to know how we did it? - Not really.
- 那好, 因为大都是靠运气 - 在哪里?
- Good,'cause it was mostly luck. - Where?
荒野区, 大瀑布市国家公园
Wilderness area, Great Falls National Park.
- Tony, 你带队 - 好的
- Tony,you lead the team. - Right.
- 你去哪儿, 老大? - 经过了十年
- Where you going,Boss? - After ten years,
我终于有一些Boone还不知道的东西
I finally got something on Boone he doesn't already know about.
我的律师还是不安
My lawyer was very upset.
他想要把我移回到监狱里去
He wanted to move me back to prison.
但是别担心. 我告诉他我喜欢这儿
But don't worry. I told him I like it here.
别弄得太舒服了. 你今天就会回去
Don't get too comfortable. You're going back today.
真的? 什么事变了?
Really?What's changed?
你发现了什么, 对吧?
You found something,didn't you?
拍这些照片的地方
The site where the photos were taken
是在310度路上的265英尺处
is 265 feet on a track of 310 degrees.
我们得穿过这里
We need to get through here.
好的
Okay.
记得我教过你的毒藤的事, 对吧?
Remember what I taught you about the poison ivy,all right?
- 别告诉Cassidy - 什么?
- Don't tell Cassidy. - What?
没事
Nothing.
跟着我
Follow me.
我没事. 我没事
I'm okay. I'm okay.
很陡
This is steep.
你们小心
Watch yourselves.
如果这就是那地方, 我能明白为什么 Boone会挑上它
Well,if this is the place, I can see why Boone picked it.
远离一般常走的路
Off the beaten path,
没有硬地面来反射声音
no hard surfaces to reflect sound.
那些女孩就算把喉咙喊破也不会 有人听见
Those girls could scream their heads off and no one would hear.
没错, 这是个完美的地点
Yeah,this is the perfect spot.
伙计们
Guys,
我们是在正确的地方了
we're in the right place.
没信号
No reception.
分散开, 用胶带隔离
Spread out,tape it off.
我们得走回去打电话给Gibbs
We'll hike back and call Gibbs.
来吧, Jethro
Come on,Jethro,
我们俩都知道你就在那里
we both know you're in there.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
你在这儿做什么?
What are you doing here?
我想来看看怪物长得是什么样的
I wanted to see what the monster looks like.
他看上去没那么吓人
He doesn't look that scary.
你看了照片了?
You saw the photographs?
是的
Yeah.
做得好, McGee
You did good,McGee.
为你感到骄傲
I'm proud of you.
还有呢?
And?
还有什么?
And what?
通常你会在最后加上些侮辱的话
Well,usually you add some kind of insult at the end.
不, 我不会
No,I don't.
好了, 可能有时候会
Well,okay,maybe sometimes.
- 但关键是我们是个团队并且... - Whoa! Tony?
- But the point is we're a team and... - Whoa! Tony?
你没事吧?
You all right?
我有些, 呃, 有些受惊
I was,uh,a little startled.
因为什么?
By what?
她
Her.
她死了才有几天的时间
She couldn't have been dead more than a few days.
Tony, 你不会相信这个的
Tony,you're not going to believe it.
Boone的标记
Boone's mark.
我-我... 这儿收不到任何信号
I-I... I can't get any reception out here.
那不奇怪
That's not surprising.
可"无名地" 不是我们搜索计划的 一部分
"Butt nowhere" isn't part of our coverage plan.
我要回到卡车那儿, 试着打通电话
I'm gonna head back to the truck and try and get the call through.
好的. 告诉Gibbs我们在这儿需要 装备需要人来
Okay. Tell Gibbs we're gonna need everything and everyone on this one.
我20分钟后就回来
I'll be back in 20 minutes.
喂. Gibbs
Yeah. Gibbs.
Gibbs...
- 我们找到了Boone的弃尸地 - 干得好
- we found Boone's dumping ground. - Good work.
- 告诉Tony他得打电话给... - 我们还找了具最近的尸体
- Tell Tony he needs to call... - We also found a fresh body.
女性. 死了不到一个星期
Female. Dead less than a week.
她的背上有Boone的标记
She has Boone's mark on her back.
我想我们肯定在对付一个模仿杀手
I think we're definitely dealing with a copycat killer.
Gibbs? Gibbs, 能听到我吗?
Gibbs? Gibbs,can you hear me?
是的, 我听到你了
Yeah,I heard you.
我需要将那区域封锁. 我就来
I want the area sealed off. I'm on my way.
Tony
Tony.
有些不对劲
Something's not right.
自从Boone在NCIS出现后就没事对劲
Well,nothing has been since Boone showed up at NCIS.
不, 不. 我-我认识这个女孩
No,no. I-I know this girl.
你认识她? 怎么会?
You know her? How?
你也认识她. 她是最后进Boone的 剪贴簿的--
You know her,too.She was the last entry in Boone's scrapbook--
Jane Doe其中的一个
one of the Jane Does.
他在受死名单上已经十年了, McGee
He's been on death row for ten years,McGee.
她在这儿不超过一个星期.
She's been here less than a week.
不可能啊
It's not possible.
不会的
It can't be.
你看上去有些憔悴, Jethro
You look a little peaked,Jethro.
有什么不对吗?
Something wrong?
也许我能帮上忙
Maybe I can help.
- 有个新进展 - 可能吧?
- A new development, - perhaps?
我得交给你了, Boone 我已经尽了力
I got to hand it to you,Boone. I did my best.
但你使我在玩你的游戏--祝贺你
But you got me to play your game-- congratulations.
你找到尸体了. 很好
You found the bodies. Good.
不是你所期望的, 对吗?
Not what you were expecting, was it?
你瞧, 现在那外面有另外某人--
You see,there's someone else out there now--
一个新的威胁--
a new threat--
而我是唯一的一个能帮你找到他的人
and I'm the only one who can help you find him.
你得要求对我的处决延期
You'll have to request a stay of my execution.
不得不传达这个意思了. Mm-mm
Gonna have to pass on that. Mm-mm.
不管这出戏怎么演法
No matter how this plays out,
周六你都将会坐在那张椅子上
you're gonna sit in that chair Saturday.
你这方面改不了这么多. 你有宣誓 过的职责
You can't have changed this much. You have a sworn duty.
可能吧, 十年前的话
Maybe ten years ago.
现在...见鬼吧...
- Now... - hell...
我能等到周日再开始调查
I can wait till Sunday to start an investigation.
- 你在虚张声势 - 36小时后你就死了
- You're bluffing. - You're dead in 36 hours.
那么, 你要是改主意了我会在这儿的
Yeah,well, I'll be here when you change your mind.
Cassidy!
好极了! 她迷路了
Great! She's lost.
为什么你不给她你的GPS玩意儿 实习的?
Why didn't you give her your GPS thingie,Probie?
她没有迷路
She's not lost.
出什么事了?!
What's going on?!
她给绑架了
She's been kidnapped.
McGee, 那自Boone坐监以来
McGee,where is my list of every visitor and phone call
关于他所有访客和电话的单子呢?
Boone's had since being in prison?
正在弄, 老大
Working it,boss.
Tony?
Tony!
- 支援队到位了吗? - 是的
- Backup teams in place? - Yeah.
我不应该那样让她独自去的, 老大
I never should've let her take off like that alone,Boss.
Cassidy的照片很干净; 没有指纹 也没有DNA
The Polaroid of Cassidy's clean; there's no prints,no DNA.
对不起, Gibbs, 我把事情搞砸了
I'm sorry,Gibbs, I screwed this whole thing up.
你搞砸了?
You screwed it up?
我们应该知道有不只一个杀手的--
We should've known there was more than one killer--
我只查了Boone被抓前的Jane Does
I only ran the Jane Does up until the time Boone was captured.
那所有的四个人都是在过去三年中 失踪的
All four have gone missing in the last three years.
着重在过去三年中Boone的联系人
Concentrate on Boone's contacts over the past three years.
是
Yeah.
我们不能再失去另一个探员了 我受不了
We can't lose another agent. I can't take this.
好了, 现有最好的猜测是个叫做 John Frederick Briggs的人
Okay,our best bet is a guy named John Frederick Briggs.
在过去三年中
In the last three years,
他打了229个电话给Boone并去探望 了他96次
he's logged 229 phone calls and visited Boone 96 times.
他在写Boone的自传
He's writing Boone's biography.
- 他就活在里面 - 他倒是有个不错的开端
- He's living it. - He's off to a good start.
1991年从军队"不名誉退伍"
Dishonorable discharge from the army in '91.
在2000年因为家庭骚乱而被捕
Arrested for domestic disturbance in 2000
- 因为打他的女朋友 - 找到他
- for beating his girlfriend. - Find him.
家庭住址和手机号码
Home address and cell phone number.
看看他的手机是否有GPS定位器...
Find out if his cell has a GPS locator...
- 查查运营商 - 它有的
- Checked the carrier. - It does,
如果报告被偷的话能由公司 远程启动
and it can be remotely activated by the company if it's reported stolen.
- 做得好, McGee - 做得好, McGee
- Good job,McGee. - Good job,McGee.
出发
Let's roll.
好了, Briggs的手机供应商正在将 他人的位置转给我们
Okay,Briggs' cell provider is relaying us his location.
他在移动
He's in movement.
他正在190号公路上向西离开市区
He's headed out of DC on the 190 West.
他在奥克利下了190号公路
He's getting off the 190 at Oakley.
如果你在麦卡锡下线的话 你可能能赶在他前头
If you get off at MacArthur, you might make it before him.
- 他在前面多远处? - 少于一英里
- How far ahead is he? - Less than a mile.
那一定就是他
That's got to be him.
把你的手放在方向盘上! 留在上面!
Keep your hands on the wheel! Keep 'em up!
好吧, 到底发生了什么事?
Okay,what the hell's going on here?
她在哪儿, Briggs?
Where is she,Briggs?
好吧. 好吧, 我有权利在这里
Okay. Okay,I have every right to be here.
听个守卫说你们找到了尸体
Heard from a guard you found the bodies.
- 我想来看看 - 闭嘴
- I want to see 'em. - Shut up.
嗨
Hello.
你对我做了些什么?
What did you do to me?
我用把铲子敲了你的头, 我亲爱的
I hit you in the head with a shovel, my dear.
是你杀了那个我们找到的女人?
Did you kill that woman we found?
是我干的
I did.
那儿还有多少个, O'Neill?
How many more are there,O'Neill?
让我想想, 那儿有...
Let's see,there was...
那儿有一个, 那儿有两个 三个, 四个...
there was one, and there was two,three,four...
加上你就五个了
You will make five.
Boone是怎样将他的律师变成他的 接替人的呢?
How did Boone turn his lawyer into his replacement?
你真以为我是凑巧做了Boone的律师 的吗? 得了!
Do you really think I'm Boone's lawyer by coincidence?Come on!
明白吗, 我...
See,I...
我把Boone挑出来的
I sought Boone out.
为什么?
Why?
我可以从他那儿学
So I could learn from him.
从最好的那里学
Learn from the best.
而你...
And you...
你就是我的毕业礼物
you're my graduation present.
要知道, 如果你想的话你可以大叫--
You know,you can scream if you want to--
这是被允许的
it's allowed.
Kyle说他想要Gibbs探员记住他
Kyle says he wants Agent Gibbs to remember him
在他死后要很久很久 所以你和我...
for a long,long time after he's gone. So you and me...
...我们会把这个进行得
...we're gonna take this
又慢又漂亮
nice and slow.
一个斗士, huh?
a fighter,huh?
以前没碰到过那样的
I haven't had one of those before.
你想用那把刀再试试吗?
You want to try that thing again with that knife?
你想要看你的剪贴簿?
You wanted to see your scrapbook?
我的探员在哪里?
Where is my agent?
住手, 住...
Stop,st...
住手
Stop.
你不知道你在做...
Look,you don't know what you're d...
你不知道你在做什么
You don't know what you're doing.
- Jethro... 不要... - 可恶!
- Jethro... don't... - Damn it.
我不知道她在哪里
I don't know where she is.
我怎么能?
How can I?
求你?
Please?
只要让我再最后一次看看她们, 拜托?
Just let me see them one last time, please?
我-我求求你
I'm-I'm begging you.
- 我求你了 - 她... 在哪儿?
- I'm begging you. - Where... is she?
我们都知道你不能毁掉证物
We all know you can't destroy evidence.
真可怜, Jethro
Pathetic,Jethro.
你真以为我需要那个来看她们
Do you really think that I needthat to see them,
而我想看的任何时候她们都在这儿?
when they're all up here anytime I want?
你的探员会受苦的
Your agent is gonna suffer.
在她身上释放出来的猥亵 是传奇性的--
The obscenities unleashed on her, legendary--
你知道为什么吗? 因为你是那个 阻止了我的人...
you know why?Because you're the one that stopped me...
这都是你犯的错!
This is all your fault!
他现在正在从她的嘴里把她的舌头 割出来
He's cutting her tongue out of her mouth right now.
要知道最精彩的部分吗?
You know the best part?
在我死后...
After I'm gone...
尸体只会不断地垒起来
bodies are just gonna continue to pile up.
开枪啊
Shoot.
开枪, 你应该开枪打死我, 你这傻瓜
Shoot me,you're supposed to shoot me,you idiot.
那就是你花了十年工夫计划 出来的大计划?
That the big plan you spent ten years working on?
让我谋杀你
Get me to murderyou
而毁了我自己的生活?
and ruin my own life?
他现在正在她的背上刻你的名字
He's carving your name in her back right now.
游戏结束了, 回到你的等死行列里吧
- Game's over. - Back to death row.
Gibbs?
Gibbs
Gibbs.
州长打电话了吗?
The governor call yet?
因为他们现在还不能杀我
'Cause they're not gonna kill me now.
我是唯一能指认杀手的人
I'm the only one who can identify the killer.
嘿, 你认为在他割掉她舌头的时候
Hey,do you think she screamed
她会叫吗, Jethro?
when he cut out her tongue,Jethro?
我不知道
I don't know.
为什么你不自己问问她呢?
Why don't you ask her yourself?
恐怕你的律师明天赶不上你的死刑了
I'm afraid your lawyer's gonna miss your execution tomorrow.
他像是死了
He's kind of dead.
享受地狱吧
Enjoy hell.
不!
No!
不...!
No...!
不!
No!
[NCIS 海军罪案调查处] 第三季 第三集